♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Peter, I need you to take
Chris and Meg to school.
Today's the day I finally
kill that squirrel
that's been eating our tomatoes.
Try to get, like, eight
of them this time.
I want to make bruschetta.
Oh, can't the kids just walk?
You know I like to watch two
full movies before I go to work.
No, Peter, they can't
walk, it's three miles.
Fine, I'll take them.
But you better keep those goggles
'cause I'm gonna put them
to good use tonight.
Once the floor is full of sawdust,
we can eat peanuts in here.
Dad, are you sure it's okay
that we took Brian's car?
Yeah, it's his own fault.
He's the one who keeps
his key in the visor
like a carefree hillbilly.
Okay, everybody out.
I don't want the cool kids
to know I'm your dad.
Hey, Chris.
Guess who I just scored as my
date to the homecoming dance.
- Vice Principal McGuire.
- Really?
Yeah, her husband just died of ALS,
so she is ready to get at it.
Hey there, strong guy.
Not now, Brenda!
She says I have the body of a
50-year-old before it gets ALS.
So who are you gonna go with?
I was thinking of asking Kara Morris.
Why don't you ask her now?
Her locker's right over there.
Um... y... uh, yeah, okay.
Hi, Kara.
I was wondering, um, if you'd like to go
to the homecoming dance with me?
Oh, hi, robot from Big Hero 6.
No, but thank you.
His name is Baymax, you gorgeous moron!
All right, red light.
Time to text and shave
and whittle and floss.
- Thanks for getting here so quickly.
- What?
I'm sorry. You're in a Prius.
I just assumed you were my Uber.
I don't know what that is
on account of being dull.
Uber... it's like a cab
except it feels like a game
'cause it's from your phone.
Anyway, I'm late for a meeting.
Can I just give you 20
bucks to drop me off?
Wow, 20 bucks just to
drive you across town?
Maybe I should be an Uber driver.
I mean, I could use the extra money.
And it's got to be easier than
when I was delivering pizzas.
All right, push. Push.
Come on, come on, almost there.
Almost there, just one more push.
Here it is!
Oh, it's half Hawaiian.
I believe that's ours.
You poor fool.
Hey, Stewie.
What's up, big guy?
None of the girls at school want
to go to homecoming with me.
Probably 'cause everyone calls
me names like "Big Nips"
and "Fat Nips" and "Big Fat Nips."
Oh, don't listen to them, Big Fat Nips.
They're just being haters.
What's a "hater"?
Oh, it's just something people say
instead of working to
change their own flaws.
Anyway, you just got to
do what Taylor Swift does
and shake it off.
Who's Taylor Swift?
Oh, my God!
Am I about to introduce
you to Taylor Swift?
W-What is she, a singer?
She's much more than a singer, Chris.
She's... she's... she's the queen!
A goddess!
A gazelle in a high-waisted swimsuit!
Uh, sorry, if you're neither insane,
nor clowns, nor a posse,
I'm not interested.
I have an idea.
You should ask Taylor Swift
to the homecoming dance!
What? Why would she go
to a dance with me?
I'm telling you, this is exactly
the kind of thing she would do.
She's such a sweetheart.
Oh, I'm going limp.
I'm just gonna lie here moaning,
thinking about Taylor Swift.
Tay-Tay.
How would I even ask her?
Oh, it's easy. You and I
will just make a video
about how sad you are and put it online.
She's very interactive
with all her fans.
I guess it's worth a shot.
Of course it is.
If she says yes, you'll
surprise everyone,
just like you did on New Year's Eve.
Three, two, one!
Some animals give me boners!
Hi. Uh, I'd like to be an Uber driver.
Okay, sure. Welcome aboard.
Don't I... don't I need
to fill out a form or...?
Oh, right, yeah, of course.
"Name."
Peter Griffin.
"Criminal history."
This section is optional.
I will skip this.
And done.
Here you go. Yeah, none
of this really matters.
All I need to know is:
do you have a car,
a phone and a face?
It's my dog's car.
Oh, and I know you didn't ask,
- but I am quick to anger.
- Okay, great.
Now get out there and try to
kiss as many ladies as you can.
The record is 60 in a month.
You, sir, are officially an Uber driver.
This is some good stuff, Chris.
I think it's ready to post.
Actually, Stewie, I changed my mind.
I made my own video and posted it.
What? How could you do that?
Stewie, I didn't want to
do all that fancy stuff,
so I just did a video of me
speaking from the heart.
You know, telling her
how much it would mean
if a girl like her went to
homecoming with a guy like me.
I couldn't even stay awake
during that description.
Hey, she already posted a response.
What?!
Hey, Chris Griffin.
I just saw your video,
and I'd love to go to
your dance with you.
All right, I got to go
eat an ice cream cone.
'Cause us stars are just like you.
Oh, my God!
Uh-oh. This means I have an
awkward phone call to make.
What? No, no, it was stupid.
What, two guys going to homecoming?
I-I assumed it was a
goof this whole time.
Take it out.
I'm ugly and unlovable.
Good evening. I'm Tom Tucker.
Our top story tonight,
pop star Taylor Swift
is coming to Quahog
to attend a dance with local
high-schooler Chris Griffin.
But first we go to commercial
while our sports reporter smiles
and spins a football for some reason.
Wow, Chris, I'm so excited!
You actually have a
date with Taylor Swift!
Thanks, Mom. Did I do good?
Can I wear Grandpa's jacket now?
I-I don't know why you
always ask for that.
Th-That's not a thing in our family.
Oh, Rupert, I can't believe Taylor Swift
is actually going to be in our house.
I haven't been this excited
since I abused those caffeine pills
to get ready for the big show.
Everything will be fine, as
long as I take one of these.
Pills? You actually are taking drugs?
Stewie, give me those.
I can't, Zach! I need them to sing!
♪ I'm so excited, I'm so excited ♪
I'm... so... scared!
Screech is going to stab
someone on Christmas.
Oh, Chris, you look so
handsome in your tux.
This must be how Meat Loaf
looked when he went to the prom.
Oh, that must be her!
Hi. You must be Chris. I'm Taylor.
What's up?!
It's so nice to finally meet you.
Your video was so sweet.
And I can't wait to go
to the dance tonight.
Me, too.
Would you like to come in?
Hi. Peter Griffin, leering dad.
Quick question: in "Shake It Off,"
you invite us to get down to,
quote, "this sick beat."
Yet the beat you then
provide is rather mild.
My question is this:
may I lick your legs?
Hi, Taylor. Stewie Griffin.
I'm your biggest fan.
I don't mean that like
a psycho, I just...
I-I'm not, I'm not a psycho!
Oh, you're a cutie.
Okay, so let's talk about Harry Styles.
Now, you don't have to say anything.
I'm just gonna slowly pull
out this tape measure,
and you indicate when I should stop.
Okay, here I go.
Still going.
Oh, my God, you bitch! Seriously?
Taylor, this is my sister
Meg and our dog Brian.
Nice to meet you both.
We're not all so impressed.
I've met Dan Aykroyd.
I'm sorry, uh, which cast
member of Hee Haw are you?
Will... you... be... nice!
Okay, well, we should probably go.
It was so nice to meet you all,
except for the girl and the dog.
Sorry about my family.
Don't apologize. They seem nice.
Well, you wouldn't say that if
you ever saw us at the movies.
All right, we got our popcorn from home,
our soda from home, our snacks from home
and Braveheart.
- Where you headed?
- The airport.
Great. Just a couple of errands
and we'll get you there.
That was one bitch of a class.
Anyways, what time's your flight?
It's in 20 minutes!
Oh, boy, I can't make it in 20 minutes.
I better call you a Lyft.
Come on, hurry up, get in!
I hope you like The Offspring.
Let's go!
Oh, my God! Taylor Swift!
She's here with him?
You guys, Mr. Buell's taking
a door-open dook in the bathroom!
I hope this isn't too boring for you.
No, this is so cool!
I always sing about high school,
but I've never actually
seen one in person.
Would you like to dance?
Sure. But you're gonna
have to stand back,
like, five and a half feet.
Cool!
You dance like an unattended fire hose.
Wow! It's like your dance
tells a whole story.
Right?
You are the only one
who's ever gotten that.
Usually people just shove
a wallet in my mouth
and call 911.
You know, Chris, I'm
having a great time.
You're so cool and down-to-earth.
I like you, too, Taylor.
I was scared meeting a celebrity,
but you're so nice and normal.
I feel totally comfortable around you.
Well, why don't you
just kiss her, Griffin?
Sorry, I just smoked a joint
with the pickup truck kids.
That was really fun, Chris.
I hope you don't mind I made the band
pay me a royalty for each
of my songs they played.
Of course not.
And I hope you didn't mind
I showed you who every
locker belongs to.
No, I thought that was nice.
I've never had a locker.
I just keep my stuff in stupid mansions.
Can I finger you?
Sure!
Hi. I'm Taylor Swift.
I'm famous, but I'm really nice.
Aw, that's one of the best
fingerings I've ever had.
What are you working on there, Chris?
Oh, I'm making a collage for Taylor
of some of her favorite things.
Here's flowers and crop tops
and pictures of Kanye
West with his mouth shut.
Wow, you two seem to have
a wonderful connection.
We do, Mom.
You know, she's the first girl
to ever really understand me.
Uh, you guys?
You might want to see this video
Bonnie posted on Facebook.
Why are you on Bonnie's Facebook page?
'Cause she's a (BLEEP) smoke-show.
♪ 'Cause I know you're ♪
♪ Just blubber in a dress shirt ♪
♪ He licked his armpit ♪
♪ Then ate all my dinner and dessert ♪
♪ Chris Griffin is a pig in every way ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Blubber, blubber, blubber, oh ♪
♪ Blubber, blubber, oh. ♪
Oh, and some animals give him boners.
What the hell?
Why would she do this?
Wait, wait, wait.
What's that next video?
Oh, Daughtry!
I'm a mom, so I love this.
Chris, what happened?
I-I thought you said Taylor had
a good time the other night.
We did!
She even let me grab
the part of her body
which on others would be a butt.
Wow, look at these comments.
Everyone hates you, Chris.
She's right. Check it out.
You're already a meme.
Aw, man, Chris, this
computer is telling me
that you done Swifted up.
Why would she do something like this?
Because this is what Taylor Swift does.
She gets into relationship with guys,
sabotages them, and then
writes angry songs about it.
I just wish I could talk to her.
Well, why can't we? She has
a house in Rhode Island.
We could go today.
Oh, my God, we can go today!
My schedule is wide-ass open!
Well, we can't just show up there.
Why not? We've done
crazier things before.
Remember when we sent that tweet?
All right, you ready?
Freeze!
We're the Internet police!
You guys are going away for a long time.
Hey, what are you in for?
I said Caitlyn Jenner
wasn't brave and beautiful.
Brian, there's some bad people in here.
Hey, what's up? I'm just
going to Quahog Stadium.
Okay, would you like the
AC on or the windows down?
How about both?
Pretty great, right?
It is! It really is!
Thank you, genius person!
No problem.
Hey, you ever go in a hot tub
when it's snowing outside?
Oh... What?!
Ms. Swift, your
songwriting team is here.
We got a socko tune for you, Taylor.
Hit it, Morty!
♪ Lox and bagels and bagels and lox ♪
♪ I like being a girl. ♪
Okay, one thought.
What if we change "lox" to "boys"
and "bagels" to "problems"?
Oh, that's perfect.
Like when you changed "pickle it good"
to "shake it off."
All right, we got our homework.
Hi, Taylor.
Chris? What are you guys doing here?
I wanted to talk to you.
Your house is way nicer
than Anne Murray's.
We broke in there, too.
Taylor, why'd you write
that song about me?
I thought we had a real connection.
We do. I really like you, Chris.
I just...
I'm sorry. I always do this.
I ruin relationships with
nice guys and John Mayer
just so I can write songs about
heartbreak and moving on.
But don't you think that's unhealthy?
You're never gonna find
a real relationship
if you keep doing this.
Listen, I'm sorry I hurt
your feelings, Chris.
Let me make it up to you.
Why don't you guys all come to
my show tonight as my guests?
Are you serious?!
Backstage with Taylor Swift?
Well, that'll be even cooler
than when I was in that remake
of The Princess Bride with Bill Cosby.
Now, one of these has the
iocane powder, you see,
and one of them makes you go
sleepy-bye with your mouth open.
Hey, pal, where we heading again?
Just go down this dark alley.
What the hell's going on?
This is what we do to Uber
drivers in this town.
Stop! Stop! Please stop!
The sound of your leather
jackets is excruciating!
You can't just buy a phone
and become a cab driver!
Please, I have two families!
Stay back!
Where-where did you get that?
Judd Hirsch himself.
I was a boy, no more than 11 or 12.
Was on the side of the road.
Man with a hat pulled up next to me.
Said I reminded him of
him when he was my age.
I was just a boy husking corn.
Didn't know what it meant.
Of course, we were all
husking corn back then
just to keep the lights on.
And you burned my car
while I was telling my
fake Judd Hirsch story.
God, I hate everybody
who's not backstage.
This next song is a new one.
It's about my boyfriend Chris.
♪ I'm pretty and I'm
rich and I'm in love ♪
♪ Me Taylor ♪
♪ I've met the guy that
I've been dreaming of ♪
♪ Me Taylor... ♪
Wow, they hate it.
This stinks!
We like you when you're miserable!
You guys, Mr. Buell's taking a
door-open dook in the bathroom!
Why were they being so mean to you?
Well, I guess they're
just used to me being sad
and hurt by men.
But I don't care if they like it, Chris.
I'm happy with you.
I'm happy with you, too.
But it doesn't seem like
your fans like this
new happy Taylor.
Are you willing to risk losing them
and jeopardize your career
and your art just for us?
I think I am.
Oh, well, I don't know if am.
What? What are you saying?
I'm saying that
Taylor Swift, you are a
spoiled ostrich-legged,
no talent, big-footed freak.
You pretend to relate to your fans,
but you make your bodyguards
carry your purse.
All your songs sound the same.
And your cats aren't that cute.
Thank you, Chris.
This next song is about
my dumb ex-boyfriend,
who either mistreated me, cheated on me
or went to massage parlors
when I was out of town.
Wow, Chris, that was really nice of you.
Yeah, I guess.
Don't worry, there'll be
plenty of girls for you.
No one will ever be close
to as good as her,
but we'll find you someone.
What about, like, a motorcycle lady?
You know, like an old gal?
Her grandchildren call
her by her first name?
Let's get out of here.
I called us an Uber.
How many tooths
is not enough tooths?
Well, kids, your father
may have gotten beat up,
but Uber's still a great job
for anyone afraid to sell their blood.
And, Chris, I'm sorry it didn't work out
with you and Taylor Swift.
I think we're all sorry
about that, Brian,
but I'm afraid we are out of time.
I would like to thank our
guests Taylor Swift,
Chris Griffin, Stewie and Brian,
Cleveland Brown and his
band of Brown Renown.
Hey, we'll see you down in
Brown Town, huh, Cleveland?
Oh, I ain't even gonna go there, Peter.
We apologize to the greased-up deaf guy.
Didn't have time for him tonight,
but let's see if we can
get him back next week
when Amanda Peet will be here
with stand-up Dom Irrera.
Good night, everybody.
Thank you for watching "We Bare Bears" on
www.CN-fan.ru